export default [
    {
        question: "1st Question : Who was the first to discover india?",
        options: ["1. Sardar Vallabhai Patel","2. Vasco da Gama","3. C.V Raman","4. Subash Chandra Bose"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "2nd Question : Who is known as the “Iron Man” of India?",
        options: ["1. Mahatma Gandhi","2. A. P. J. Abdul Kalam","3. Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel","4. Bhimrao Ramji Ambedkar"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "3rd Question : What is the Capital of India?",
        options: ["1. Varanasi","2. Agra","3. Mumbai","4. New Delhi"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "4th Question : Which state is also known as the “fruit bowl” of India?",
        options: ["1. Himachal Pradesh","2. Delhi","3. Kashmir","4. kerala"],
        answer: 0,
    },
    {
        question: "5th Question : Which is the national sport of India?",
        options: ["1. Badminton","2. Football","3. Cricket","4. Hockey"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "6th Question : Which state is also known as the “land of rising sun”?",
        options: ["1. Andra","2. Arunachal Pradesh","3. Karnataka","4. Tamilnadu"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "7th Question : Where is the Taj Mahal located?",
        options: ["1. Agra","2. New Delhi","3. Singapore","4. Angamaly"],
        answer: 0,
    },
    {
        question: "8th Question : Which Indian state has the smallest coastline?",
        options: ["1. Rajasthan","2. Gujarat","3. Goa","4. Bihar"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "9th Question : What is the national heritage animal of India?",
        options: ["1. Tiger","2. Lion","3. Jirafa","4. Elephant"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "10th Question : In which state is the International Kite Festival celebrated?",
        options: ["1. Haryana","2. Gujarat","3. Uttar Pradesh","4. West Bengal"],
        answer: 1,
    },
]